In terms of company numbers,
the company has always grown except in
2008, or it has had a lot of growth
recently while in the past it was
bigger, or it was smaller, or it
was bigger before, now it is smaller.
How did it go more or less?
The company, in fact, apart from some
very difficult times, has always had
excellent financial health and also,
let's say, a turnover that is
always showing a small growth, they have
never been incredible.  What
we are doing more and more is
improving ebidity.  It's not so much a
question of producing incredible quantities and
scattering fabrics all over the world;
on the contrary, we are learning to produce less and
less, and this too is a question of
sustainability.  Here, we are learning
to perform
economically
within parameters.
Looking ahead, how long do you imagine yourself staying
here?  What do you see for the future
of the company for the next
generations?  This is an answer that is
not just up to me.  Of course, there's
something we also talk about with the Zegna family
.  it is an objective that laenda is
a
social asset because it has people inside and
therefore companies are not things
that can be shut down with Giovanni or
Lorenzo who will retire tomorrow
because we often ask ourselves and after
us since we are not infinite who comes
today you have seen a lot of kids I
am so happy that the kids are
better than me and they must be better than
me.  So the company has its
place, it is autonomous and it moves forward.